<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo noupdate="1">

    <!-- Water Tank Cleaning — transcribed from real Aaban quotes/contracts
         (DR.SAMI BUILDING Contract 968/26; Medco Contracting Quote 495/26).
         Editable in the UI afterwards. -->
    <record id="agreement_template_water_tank" model="fm.contract.agreement.template">
        <field name="name">Water Tank Cleaning — Standard</field>
        <field name="service_line">water_tank</field>
        <field name="quotation_intro_text">We are thankful for the interest and confidence shown towards our services. With reference to the subject inquiry, please find our competitive proposal for water tank cleaning and disinfection as follows.</field>
        <field name="scope_method_text">Our process starts with the deep cleaning of the entire water tank: draining out the existing water, cleaning the interior tanks, disinfection, washing and flushing the tanks, refilling the tanks with fresh water, and laboratory testing.</field>
        <field name="service_text">Aaban will provide Water Tank Cleaning and Disinfection at the site stated above, in accordance with the schedule detailed in this agreement. The tanks will be cleaned and disinfected as per Municipality standards and guidelines using environmentally friendly chemicals approved by the Municipality. Stains, sediment and mould are removed with brushes, and the tanks are thoroughly rinsed with fresh water and checked for pH neutrality before refilling.</field>
        <field name="schedule_text">The customer agrees to fulfil all technical guidelines requested by Aaban to secure the best results. Tanks should be drained by the client prior to the scheduled arrival of the cleaning team, or the client should provide access with the tank at 5-10% of water level or empty.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="agreement_template_water_tank_line_safety" model="fm.contract.agreement.template.line">
        <field name="template_id" ref="agreement_template_water_tank"/>
        <field name="sequence">10</field>
        <field name="name">Safety</field>
        <field name="body">Aaban carries out all work strictly in accordance with the highest safety standards. All technicians are trained in all aspects of safety, are well supervised to ensure operations run smoothly, and are equipped with the required PPE (goggles, gloves, safety shoes, safety belts) and instruments for this process.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="agreement_template_water_tank_line_tank_details" model="fm.contract.agreement.template.line">
        <field name="template_id" ref="agreement_template_water_tank"/>
        <field name="sequence">20</field>
        <field name="name">Tank Details</field>
        <field name="body">[Fill in for this site: tank type(s), capacity in USG, and total number of tanks — e.g. "RCC underground tank (30,000 USG x 1); GRP panel tank (5,000 USG x 1); total 2 tanks, 35,000 USG."]</field>
    </record>

    <record id="agreement_template_water_tank_line_customer_resp" model="fm.contract.agreement.template.line">
        <field name="template_id" ref="agreement_template_water_tank"/>
        <field name="sequence">30</field>
        <field name="name">Customer Responsibility</field>
        <field name="body">1. Tanks will be drained by the client prior to the scheduled arrival of the cleaning team, or the client will provide the tank at 5-10% of water level or empty.
2. Client to provide 220V single-phase electricity supply and water supply (60 litre/min) near the working location.
3. Work permit to be prepared in advance.
4. Client to ensure proper access is available to all units.
5. Client to arrange all passes and permits required for the vehicle and operator at the service location, or parking during service time.
6. Safe storage for Aaban's equipment until completion of work.
7. Waste disposal facility for removed debris.
8. An authorised person/staff should be present for verification and the completion report upon completion of each area.
9. Leftover water below suction level in the tanks will be drained by the operator into the client's drainage system.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="agreement_template_water_tank_line_report" model="fm.contract.agreement.template.line">
        <field name="template_id" ref="agreement_template_water_tank"/>
        <field name="sequence">40</field>
        <field name="name">After Service Report</field>
        <field name="body">Photographs will be taken before and after the work and included in the final report. The service report will be issued within 8-10 working days after completion of work.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="agreement_template_water_tank_line_terms" model="fm.contract.agreement.template.line">
        <field name="template_id" ref="agreement_template_water_tank"/>
        <field name="sequence">50</field>
        <field name="name">Additional Contract Terms</field>
        <field name="body">As per the relevant Municipality's guidelines, the rooftop tank should be cleaned only after cleaning the main supply tank. If the client requests cleaning of the rooftop tank only and the water sample subsequently tests positive, Aaban will not be responsible for re-cleaning or re-sampling.</field>
    </record>

    <!-- Anti-Termite Treatment — transcribed from a real Aaban quote
         (AL SIKKA BUILDING CONT Quote 129/25, pre-construction termite
         control). Editable in the UI afterwards. -->
    <record id="agreement_template_termite" model="fm.contract.agreement.template">
        <field name="name">Anti-Termite Treatment — Standard</field>
        <field name="service_line">termite</field>
        <field name="scope_method_text">Operations are carried out as per the relevant Municipality's stated/approved procedures and terms and conditions for pre-construction termite control, typically across three stages: Stage 1 — PCC &amp; RCC; Stage 2 — vertical and horizontal treatment inside the tie beams; Stage 3 — vertical and horizontal treatment outside the tie beams.</field>
        <field name="service_text">Aaban will provide anti-termite treatment at the site stated above, in accordance with the treatment type and materials/methods detailed in this agreement, using procedures approved by the relevant Municipality.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="agreement_template_termite_line_treatment_type" model="fm.contract.agreement.template.line">
        <field name="template_id" ref="agreement_template_termite"/>
        <field name="sequence">10</field>
        <field name="name">Treatment Type</field>
        <field name="body">[Specify for this contract: e.g. "Spray (pre-construction)."]</field>
    </record>

    <record id="agreement_template_termite_line_materials" model="fm.contract.agreement.template.line">
        <field name="template_id" ref="agreement_template_termite"/>
        <field name="sequence">20</field>
        <field name="name">Materials and Methods</field>
        <field name="body">1. All services will be provided as per the relevant Municipality's approved procedures.
2. All equipment and control treatment methods will conform to the standards set by the Municipality.
3. Aaban will inform the Second Party at least one day before treatment, by mutual agreement, and will arrange a representative for collaboration.
4. On-site electricity and water availability will be arranged/confirmed by the Second Party.
5. The Second Party will provide polythene sheeting of the required length and quality.
6. The Second Party will provide Aaban with access to the areas to be serviced.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="agreement_template_termite_line_warranty" model="fm.contract.agreement.template.line">
        <field name="template_id" ref="agreement_template_termite"/>
        <field name="sequence">30</field>
        <field name="name">Warranty Certificate</field>
        <field name="body">Aaban will provide a ten (10) year warranty for the treated areas as per the scope of treatment and service area reports. The payment amount is charged at the rate given per square metre. During the warranty period, services for the treated area will be provided without additional cost. The warranty applies to the treated area only.</field>
    </record>

    <!-- Deep Cleaning — transcribed from real Aaban quotes (Villa 52 Al
         Barsha Quote 6/25; Montreal Management Consultants Quote 941/26 &
         Contract 838/25). Generic/branch-blank — issued the same way
         regardless of site or branch in every document seen. -->
    <record id="agreement_template_cleaning_deep" model="fm.contract.agreement.template">
        <field name="name">Deep Cleaning — Standard</field>
        <field name="service_line">cleaning_deep</field>
        <field name="quotation_intro_text">We are thankful for the interest and confidence shown towards our service for deep cleaning. With reference to the subject inquiry, please find our competitive proposal for the same as follows.</field>
        <field name="scope_method_text">Deep cleaning covers, as applicable to the site: toilets (cabinets, drawers, sink and faucet descaling, shower head, walls, seat, exhaust fan, flooring, mirrors and glass doors); kitchen (sink and faucet descaling, walls, hood and countertop de-greasing, flooring); general areas (cabinets, light fixtures, AC grills, walls, corners, windows and frames, glass and wooden doors); flooring (ceramic, wooden and marble, machine-scrubbed, paint-mark removal where possible); ceiling (AC ventilation grills, corners, lights and spot lights); and external areas (balcony/parking floor, handrails and corners, where accessible).</field>
        <field name="service_text">Aaban will provide Deep Cleaning services at the site stated above, in accordance with the scope and schedule detailed in this agreement, using scrubber machines and appropriate cleaning agents for each surface type.</field>
    </record>

    <!-- Pest Control — Dubai. Dubai-issued Pest Control contracts follow a
         materially different, Dubai Municipality-specific legal framework
         (Local No. 11 of 2003) from the generic Ajman-issued wording —
         different license number, different visit cadence rules, different
         reporting obligations. Transcribed from real Aaban contracts issued
         by the Dubai branch (ZOWMI GROCERY STORE Contract 791/26; DECOLINE
         CONSTRUCTION Contract 955/26) and a Dubai-site quotation (CLEANCO
         CLEANING SERVICES Quote 527/24). Scoped to the Dubai branch — see
         fm_branch.py for how this combines with service_line matching. -->
    <record id="agreement_template_pest_dubai" model="fm.contract.agreement.template">
        <field name="name">Pest Control — Dubai</field>
        <field name="service_line">pest</field>
        <field name="branch_id" ref="branch_dubai"/>
        <field name="quotation_intro_text">With reference to the above-mentioned subject and subsequent inspection, we are pleased to provide our best quote for pest control services. The pesticides used are strictly approved by the Ministry of Climate Change and Environment.</field>
        <field name="service_text">Public Health Pest Control Agreement — Aaban Classic Building Cleaning &amp; Pest Control Services (Dubai branch) is authorised by the Public Health Pest Control Section, Dubai Municipality, to carry out pest control operations at the Second Party's site under this agreement, as per the specifications and requirements below.</field>
        <field name="schedule_text">Instructions and Terms and Conditions are as per Municipality Local Order No. 11 of 2003. The Second Party is responsible for keeping its establishment, premises or construction site free from public health pests and for not providing a favourable environment for their breeding, for the safety of the Dubai Emirate community.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="agreement_template_pest_dubai_line_compliance" model="fm.contract.agreement.template.line">
        <field name="template_id" ref="agreement_template_pest_dubai"/>
        <field name="sequence">10</field>
        <field name="name">Dubai Municipality Compliance</field>
        <field name="body">All pest control operations are carried out as per the Dubai Sustainable Public Health Pest Control Model approved by the Public Health Pest Control Section, Dubai Municipality, which is considered an integral part of this agreement. A specific report is prepared after each operation, and a monthly report, both per Dubai Municipality's standard report formats, specifying: areas visited; date of visit; pests found and infestation level; treatments carried out; follow-up visit dates (if any); pesticides used; and instructions/recommendations.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="agreement_template_pest_dubai_line_visits" model="fm.contract.agreement.template.line">
        <field name="template_id" ref="agreement_template_pest_dubai"/>
        <field name="sequence">20</field>
        <field name="name">Visit Frequency and Reporting</field>
        <field name="body">Routine visits: two visits per month for food and beverage (F&amp;B) establishments; one visit per month for non-food establishments, premises and buildings.
Follow-up visits: where infestation is reported during a routine visit, a follow-up visit is conducted every three days until the infestation disappears, with a report prepared per the standard format.
Complaint/call-out visits: on a complaint from the Second Party, Aaban will visit the site the same day and carry out pest control operations as per the Public Health Pest Control Section Dubai Municipality standards.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="agreement_template_pest_dubai_line_pesticides" model="fm.contract.agreement.template.line">
        <field name="template_id" ref="agreement_template_pest_dubai"/>
        <field name="sequence">30</field>
        <field name="name">Pesticides and Records</field>
        <field name="body">Pesticides used must be registered with the Ministry of Climate Change and Environment and used per the manufacturer's recommendations. Aaban maintains a complete pest control file, accessible to the Second Party within 15 minutes of request, containing: in-charge contact details; a copy of this agreement; the list of pesticides used with registration certificates and MSDS; all visit and monthly reports; trap location maps; and a copy of the latest ministerial decree on banned/restricted pesticides. Fumigation or termite control operations require prior approval from the Public Health Pest Control Section, Dubai Municipality.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="agreement_template_pest_dubai_line_second_party" model="fm.contract.agreement.template.line">
        <field name="template_id" ref="agreement_template_pest_dubai"/>
        <field name="sequence">40</field>
        <field name="name">Second Party Commitments</field>
        <field name="body">The Second Party agrees to: pay Aaban the agreed amount per the agreed payment terms; prepare the necessary working permits and approvals; and take corrective action on instructions and recommendations raised by Aaban. Legal action may be taken if the Second Party's premises remain infested due to its own non-compliance (e.g. uncleared litter, trash or kitchen debris).</field>
    </record>

    <record id="agreement_template_pest_dubai_line_termination" model="fm.contract.agreement.template.line">
        <field name="template_id" ref="agreement_template_pest_dubai"/>
        <field name="sequence">50</field>
        <field name="name">Termination (Dubai Municipality Notification)</field>
        <field name="body">This contract may be terminated where: both parties agree to terminate at any time; there is no approved pest control supervisor within the company; the company is temporarily or permanently closed due to violations; or the pest control activity licence is cancelled. Either party must notify the Public Health Pest Control Section, Dubai Municipality in writing of any termination.</field>
    </record>

</odoo>
